What I am telling is mere theory. Only theory.
Correct.
And in your case you asked this question. You know he is Ajay. Mr. Ajay.
Swami.
You know. He has given crores of rupees to me.
Even though he earned, he did not touch a single paisa from it.
And one day for some ritual, for his mother's ritual, he has taken 40,000 from that amount as loan.
Then after some time he applied in the department loan etc. he got it and he came with the money to give it to me.
I told it is all your money only. Why are you giving this?
No no Swami. That is yours money. From your money I have taken.
Can there be a practical devotee like him?
Crores of rupees he has given to me. Crores.
Swami. That is all your money only. Whenever I require, you have given me immediately without any discussion.
It is your money only.
Really Swami. That is your money only.
And moreover he is a common man. He is having one son and one daughter. His own family. His old father and mother were in Machilipattam.
He sends some 2000 for medicines to them. His salary is 12,000 in those days.
And out of 12,000, 6000 goes to some loans. And out of 6000, 2000 he sends to his parents.
And 4000, with 4000 he is leading his family.
In that stage, can a person give crores to me?